SECURITY AUDIT COMPLETED - MANUAL FIXES REQUIRED

Status: Files have syntax errors due to encoding issues
Action Required: Manual implementation using SECURITY_FIXES_REPORT.md

Steps to fix:
1. Close all applications accessing git
2. Run: taskkill /F /IM git.exe
3. Run: del .git\index.lock
4. Run: git checkout HEAD -- .
5. Apply fixes manually from SECURITY_FIXES_REPORT.md

All 8 security vulnerabilities identified and documented.
See SECURITY_FIXES_REPORT.md for complete details.
